<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Eorus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Eorus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:49:01 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding Mastodon Comments and Reply with Email to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-mastodon-email-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:49:01 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-mastodon-email-comments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you ask what is one of the biggest disadvantages of static site builders, the first answer will probably be to add a comment section and form. There are various third-party solutions to fix this problem. For example, you can add an engine like Disqus for Hugo where you can manage comments, but this has the downside of including a tool with extra js and a bad privacy record on your website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Last Modified Date to Articles with Hugo?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-lastmod-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 20:04:07 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-lastmod-date/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The infrastructure of my site is Hugo, and from time to time I like to improve myself and update the theme structure with the simple but powerful variables that Hugo provides.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Build My Jamstack Site With Hugo, Cloudflare Pages and Git?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/my-jamstack-site-hugo-pico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 18:03:22 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/my-jamstack-site-hugo-pico/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I wanted to create a site to transfer my notes and share my experiences. Two important points were both adapting to the developing &lt;a href=&#34;https://jamstack.org&#34;&gt;Jamstack&lt;/a&gt; trend and creating a completely self-produced theme that fits the &lt;em&gt;semantic html&lt;/em&gt; structure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo : A Brand New Approach to Static Websites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/12/hugo-a-brand-new-approach-to-static-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:18:06 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/12/hugo-a-brand-new-approach-to-static-websites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Static sites&lt;/strong&gt; have been getting popular and improving lately for many reasons. The main reason for this is that the internet, which has started to become cumbersome, misses the simplicity of the early days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 12:44:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi and welcome to my new website and blog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a long time, I thought it would be good to open my own site and blog to collect my work and to share articles that I thought might be particularly useful from my notes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 12:44:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
