<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Eorus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Eorus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AGS Soğutma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/ags-sogutma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/ags-sogutma/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with Content and Photo Creation Client: AGS Soğutma Project date: 01 June, 2016 Project URL: www.agssogutma.com.tr AGS Soğutma Project Details For AGS Soğutma, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Skel framework that generally match the brownish colors suitable for the corporate look. I worked to include all content and products of the company on the site, and in addition, I&#39;ve made the shootings of products photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ardil Tekstil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/ardil-tekstil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/ardil-tekstil/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with Content and Photo Creation Client: Ardil Tekstil Project date: 01 June, 2016 Project URL: www.ardiltekstil.com Ardil Tekstil Project Details For Ardil Tekstil, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Bootstrap framework in shades that generally match the blue color, suitable for the corporate look. I worked to include all content and products of the company on the site, and in addition, I&#39;ve made the shootings of product and facility photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzu Odabaşı</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/arzu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/arzu/</guid>
      <description> Project information Category: One Page Template Setup Client: Arzu Odabaşı Project date: 01 September, 2018 Project URL: www.arzuodabasi.com Arzu Odabaşı Project Details This is a personal site for Arzu Odabaşı. She is President &amp; Founder of H2A H2A Corporate Management Advisory Company. I&#39;ve made the server setup as back-end development. As part of front-end, I implemented a one page resume template. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Camera News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/dailycameranews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/dailycameranews/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Camera Industry - Blogging Client: Daily Camera News Project date: 01 January, 2013 Project URL: www.dailycameranews.com Daily Camera News Details A blog that actively brings together daily camera news with the end user since the beginning of the 2010s. This website, which has English content, appeals to an intense audience together with social media channels. I have been carrying out the entire management individually for about 8 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darüşşafaka Çatı Konuşmaları</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/darussafaka-cati-konusmalari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/darussafaka-cati-konusmalari/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Front-End Development Client: Darüşşafaka Çatı Konuşmaları Project date: 01 June, 2018 Project URL: www.catikonusmalari.com Darüşşafaka Çatı Konuşmaları Project Details For Darüşşafaka Çatı Konuşmaları, I&#39;ve made the front-end development, I implemented a work on a custom Wordpress theme with Bootstrap framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darüşşafaka Physical Therapy and Rehabilitation Center</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/darussafaka-physical-therapy-rehabilitation-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/darussafaka-physical-therapy-rehabilitation-center/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Front End Development Client: Darüşşafaka Physical Therapy and Rehabilitation Center Project date: 01 July, 2020 Project URL: www.dsftr.com Darüşşafaka Physical Therapy and Rehabilitation Center Project Details For Darüşşafaka Ömran and Yahya Hamuluoğlu Physical Therapy and Rehabilitation Center, I&#39;ve made the general Wordpress setup with multilanguage support as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Bootstrap framework that is suitable for the corporate look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSMUN </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/dsmun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/dsmun/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Wordpress Theme Integration Client: Darüşşafaka MUN Project date: 01 November, 2017 Project URL: www.dsmun.org Darüşşafaka MUN Project Details Sometimes it is enjoyable to help young people and create a long-lasting and active website. In this project, we created a MUN site for Darüşşafaka students, known as Model United Nations, with all schools participating. The students decided on the content and design, which is a small copy of the United Nations, and I did the coding and wordpress integration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emaga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/emaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/emaga/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with E-commerce Client: Emaga Shop Project date: 01 November, 2018 Project URL: www.emaga.de Emaga Project Details For Emaga, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a custom theme with using Bootstrap framework.&#xA;I worked to include all content and integrated Woocommerce for shopping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enlem Balıkçılık</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-balikcilik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-balikcilik/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: İçerik ve Fotoğraf Oluşturma ile Full Stack Development Client: Enlem Balıkçılık Project date: 01 Mayıs, 2020 Project URL: www.enlembalikcilik.com Enlem Balıkçılık Enlem Balıkçılık için sunucu kurulumu, Wordpress ve veritabanı kurulumlarını back-end geliştirme olarak yaptım. Ön yüz geliştirmenin bir parçası olarak, kurumsal görünüme uygun, genellikle su ve balıkçılık terimleriyle eşleşen bir yapıda Bootstrap framework üzerine bir çalışma uyguladım.&#xA;Şirketin tüm içerik ve ürünlerini siteye dahil etmek için çalıştım, ayrıca ürün ve tesis fotoğraflarının çekimlerini yaptım.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enlem Cold Storage Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-cold-storage-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-cold-storage-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with Content and Photo Creation Client: ENLEM SOĞUK HAVA DEPOLAMA LOJİSTİK VE GIDA SANAYİ A.Ş Project date: 01 March, 2020 Project URL: www.enlemsogukhava.com Enlem Cold Storage Warehouse Project Details For Enlem Cold Storage Warehouse, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Bootstrap framework which generally matches the company logo and work area that is suitable for the corporate look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enlem Sea Food</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-sea-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-sea-food/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with Content and Photo Creation Client: Enlem Sea Food Project date: 01 June, 2020 Project URL: www.enlemseafood.com Enlem Sea Food Project Details For Enlem Sea Food, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Bootstrap framework in shades that generally match the terms aqua and fishing, suitable for the corporate look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enlem Soğuk Hava Deposu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-soguk-hava-deposu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/enlem-soguk-hava-deposu/</guid>
      <description>Project information Kategori: İçerik Üretimi ve Fotoğraf Çekimleri ile Full Stack Development Müşteri: ENLEM SOĞUK HAVA DEPOLAMA LOJİSTİK VE GIDA SANAYİ A.Ş Proje tarihi: 01 March, 2020 Proje URL: www.enlemsogukhava.com Enlem Soğuk Hava Deposu Proje Detayları For Enlem Cold Storage Warehouse, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a work on Bootstrap framework which generally matches the company logo and work area that is suitable for the corporate look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Groups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/fb-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/fb-groups/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Facebook Groups Client: Social Media of Blogging Platforms Project date: 01 September, 2013 Project URL: www.facebook.com Facebook Groups Details I regularly manage the Facebook Groups I create for each camera brand in order to reach the blog content to more masses. In addition to the moderation and regulation of these active groups with a large number of users, I share the news and review contents I produce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/fb-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/fb-pages/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Facebook Pages Client: Social Media of Blogging Platforms Project date: 01 September, 2013 Project URL: www.facebook.com Facebook Groups Details I regularly manage the Facebook Pages I create for each camera brand in order to reach the blog content to more masses. In addition to the moderation and regulation of these active groups with a large number of users, I share the news and review contents I produce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finansal Planlama Derneği</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/finansal-planlama-dernegi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/finansal-planlama-dernegi/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Full Stack Development with Content Creation Client: Finansal Planlama Derneği Project date: 01 May, 2019 Project URL: www.fpd.org.tr Finansal Planlama Derneği Project Details For FPD, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a custom theme that is suitable for the corporate look. I worked to include all content and stock photos of the company on the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fotopedi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/fotopedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/fotopedi/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Photography Website - Blogging Client: Fotopedi Project date: 01 September, 2011 Project URL: www.fotopedi.org Fotopedi Details Fotopedi, which started its publishing life as &#34;Türk Nikon&#34;, has written numerous articles on photography, shooting techniques and how to do it. For the last 5 years, the site has been continuing with the name Fotopedi in order not to stick to a brand and to continue as a photography encyclopedia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H2A Danışmanlık</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/h2a-danismanlik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/h2a-danismanlik/</guid>
      <description> Project information Category: One Page Html Setup Client: H2a Danışmanlık Project date: 01 September, 2019 Project URL: www.h2adanismanlik.com H2A Danışmanlık Project Details H2A is a freelance platform that I am a part of. I have implemented a one-page template in order to create a corporate look and meet web needs. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>İdi Lojistik</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/idi-lojistik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/idi-lojistik/</guid>
      <description>Project information Category: Wordpress Theme Integration Client: İdi Lojistik Project date: 01 November, 2019 Project URL: www.idi.com.tr İdi Lojistik Project Details For İdi Lojistik, I&#39;ve made the server setup, Wordpress and database installations as back-end development. As part of front-end development, I implemented a ready theme with custom contact form and several plugins for company needs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
