<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Eorus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Eorus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:25:39 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archlinux Pacman Commands Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/archlinux-pacman-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:25:39 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/archlinux-pacman-commands/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If we think of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linux&#34;&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; distributions as a person, package managers are the most important factors that determine the characters and structures of these people. With package managers you can install and enjoy the latest software on your desktop. &lt;strong&gt;Pacman&lt;/strong&gt;, which is a combination of the words &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Package&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Manager&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;, is the default package manager used on Arch-based systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Mastodon Comments and Reply with Email to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-mastodon-email-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:49:01 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-mastodon-email-comments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you ask what is one of the biggest disadvantages of static site builders, the first answer will probably be to add a comment section and form. There are various third-party solutions to fix this problem. For example, you can add an engine like Disqus for Hugo where you can manage comments, but this has the downside of including a tool with extra js and a bad privacy record on your website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comfort Zone, Notifications and Small Appliances</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/comfort-zone-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 13:33:20 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/comfort-zone-notifications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actually, I thought the topic of this article was digital minimalism. But I made a small change in line with some of the new publications I&amp;rsquo;ve read recently. In fact, I brought this article forward.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThinkPad X220 in 2023 and the Programs I Use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/thinkpad-x220-programs-uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:39:28 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/thinkpad-x220-programs-uses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My personal machine is a 12 year old &lt;strong&gt;Lenovo ThinkPad X220&lt;/strong&gt; that I&amp;rsquo;m running Arch with &lt;a href=&#34;https://i3wm.org/&#34;&gt;i3wm&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/baskerville/bspwm&#34;&gt;bspwm&lt;/a&gt;. I still use it fondly in 2023 and I want to continue using until it leaves me. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to make the X220 as efficient as I can with &lt;a href=&#34;https://archlinux.org/&#34;&gt;Arch Linux&lt;/a&gt; and WMs and related shortcuts. Especially in recent years, I have had a very comfortable and sustainable system by using command line applications. Presumably this is the same for anyone using any WM on Linux and customizing it and backing up the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eorus/dotfiles&#34;&gt;dotfiles&lt;/a&gt; configuration files, but for a machine with an i5-2450M processor, today&amp;rsquo;s websites and traditional programs it can be quite challenging.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Ways to Read Linux Man Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/linux-man-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:24:23 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/linux-man-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most important skills you can learn as a Linux user is how to use the man pages. In other words, mastering the man page is an important key to being comfortable and efficient when using the Linux system. Of course, very few achieve this, and we often turn to internet searches rather than manual pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Last Modified Date to Articles with Hugo?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-lastmod-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 20:04:07 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/hugo-lastmod-date/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The infrastructure of my site is Hugo, and from time to time I like to improve myself and update the theme structure with the simple but powerful variables that Hugo provides.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Featured Movies and Series I Watched in 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/featured-movies-and-series-i-watched-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 13:34:48 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/featured-movies-and-series-i-watched-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to remember that I started blogging again in 2023, I decided to transfer the part of my local notes related to movies and TV series by expanding and adding some of the contents. Here is a list of movies and TV series that impressed me, worth talking about and maybe a recommendation, I watched in 2022. I would like to publish before it was too late.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I use only GNU/Linux and Free/Libre Open-Source Software?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/why-gnu-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 16:23:54 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/why-gnu-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First of all, I think it would be right to start by noting the conceptual difference between &amp;ldquo;Free Software&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Open Source&amp;rdquo;. So let&amp;rsquo;s leave this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gnu.org/philosophy/open-source-misses-the-point.en.html&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Look at Fediverse and Decentralized Social Media Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/fediverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:26:56 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/fediverse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fediverse&lt;/strong&gt; is a collection of consolidated servers used for social media, web publishing, file hosting and other modern web activities, but able to communicate with each other while hosted independently. In this way, users can create so-called identities on different servers. The name is derived from the words &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;federation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;universe&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Gitconfig File Setup and Aliases</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/gitconfig-aliases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:55:49 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/gitconfig-aliases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; is a version control system designed and developed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linus_Torvalds&#34;&gt;Linus Torvalds&lt;/a&gt;, the creator of the Linux kernel. Git helps developers keep track of the status of their code and allows them to collaborate on a codebase. Thanks to Git, you can easily return to the copies you have made when you need, by making copies of the step-by-step versions of the projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Clean Arch Linux?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/clean-up-arch-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 17:20:56 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/clean-up-arch-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Regularly caring for the things you care about keeps them healthier and more sustainable. In this article, I will provide information on how to clean the &lt;a href=&#34;https://archlinux.org&#34;&gt;Arch Linux&lt;/a&gt; system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Build My Jamstack Site With Hugo, Cloudflare Pages and Git?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/my-jamstack-site-hugo-pico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 18:03:22 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/my-jamstack-site-hugo-pico/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I wanted to create a site to transfer my notes and share my experiences. Two important points were both adapting to the developing &lt;a href=&#34;https://jamstack.org&#34;&gt;Jamstack&lt;/a&gt; trend and creating a completely self-produced theme that fits the &lt;em&gt;semantic html&lt;/em&gt; structure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Doing Something Difficult</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/doing-hard-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:00:51 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/doing-hard-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Doing things the hard way can lead to better learning. Performing a new and challenging activity is a good way to develop and maintain cognitive skills.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo : A Brand New Approach to Static Websites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/12/hugo-a-brand-new-approach-to-static-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:18:06 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/12/hugo-a-brand-new-approach-to-static-websites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Static sites&lt;/strong&gt; have been getting popular and improving lately for many reasons. The main reason for this is that the internet, which has started to become cumbersome, misses the simplicity of the early days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 12:44:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi and welcome to my new website and blog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a long time, I thought it would be good to open my own site and blog to collect my work and to share articles that I thought might be particularly useful from my notes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 12:44:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/11/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
